

Lin Myat Oo

Computer Engineer

- +959770129422
- Yangon, Myanmar
- ☑ linmyatooa7@gmail.com

Education

Bachelor of Engineering University of Technology (Yatanarpon Cyber City) 2015-2019

BEHS No.1 Anglan 2014

Skills

Adobe tools

C Programming, C++, C#

Python

Php, Java Script , Sql ,

Html , Css

Embedded

Problem Solving, Leadership

Languages

Finglish -B2

Myanmar - Native

About Me

Motivated and results-driven Software Engineer. I have continuously demonstrated experience in improving software performance by implementing new ideas, updating, testing, and coding. Comfortable in working in fast-paced environments and delivering exceptional results in a timely manner.

Work Experiences

Software Engineer

lyi Robot Co. | 2019-2020

Worked as a website developer...

Senior Mentor

Now Maker Space | 2017-2019

Organizer

Clash of Robots | 2018-2019

WRG Myanmar | 2020

University Projects

UTYCC FYI (website project | 2015)
Robot Arm (embedded | 2016)
Camera Dolly (IoT project. | 2017)
Smart Home (IoT project. | 2018)
Smart Wheelchair (embedded | 2019)
Sumo Robot (Clash of Robot project)